[
    {
        "question": "What is your association for the radical 日?",
        "choice1": "user input",
        "choice2": "cupboard",
        "choice3": "box",
        "choice4": "rock",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your association for the radical にんべん?",
        "choice1": "stand",
        "choice2": "pin",
        "choice3": "user input",
        "choice4": "needle",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your association for 木?",
        "choice1": "mountain",
        "choice2": "sail",
        "choice3": "wheat",
        "choice4": "user input",
        "answer": 4
    }
    ,{
        "question": "What is your association for 田?",
        "choice1": "earth",
        "choice2": "user input",
        "choice3": "target",
        "choice4": "dice",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your association for 士?",
        "choice1": "user input",
        "choice2": "cross",
        "choice3": "forest",
        "choice4": "window",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your association for 女?",
        "choice1": "star",
        "choice2": "knee",
        "choice3": "mother",
        "choice4": "user input",
        "answer": 4
    }
    ,{
        "question": "What is your association for 目?",
        "choice1": "book",
        "choice2": "cupboard",
        "choice3": "user input",
        "choice4": "fence",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is your association for 小冠?",
        "choice1": "heaven",
        "choice2": "reign",
        "choice3": "user input",
        "choice4": "god",
        "answer": 3
    }
    ,{
        "question": "What is your association for 子?",
        "choice1": "snake",
        "choice2": "user input",
        "choice3": "myself",
        "choice4": "like",
        "answer": 2
    }
    ,{
        "question": "What is your association for 力?",
        "choice1": "man",
        "choice2": "shoe",
        "choice3": "axe",
        "choice4": "user input",
        "answer": 4
    }
]
